How is the situation with our house?
What house?
The house we will live in.
Why are you telling me this now?
One of my teachers here told me that the wedding gifts depend on the house, so I need to know.
Here it is.
You want to borrow $30,000, is that right?
Yes.
I can't hold it in.
Think for a bit! Why can't you do the same as Ki Joon is doing?
Why are you comparing us, it's annoying.
I will transfer the title of the apartment (condo) before you get married, apartment in Changshin-dong will be the standard
She just wants to get it over with only giving you apartment in Gangbook?
They are so stingy
Mom, please don't.
I'll take care of it.
What are you going to do?
They have an apartment in Gangnam?
They do!
You are growing well.
You're having an engagement party too?
Of course. I should do what all the others are doing.
Since we are on the topic, can you take a picture for us?
Please tell her that I can't.
I heard you're getting engaged. You're being generous
If you keep this up, we can't see each other anymore.
Am I the only one like this? Your mouth tells me to leave but your eyes tell me to come.
You were a real virgin
I am a patient.
Let's drink some coffee.
Are you entering Miss Korea? Why are you waving your hand?
Hyung, please take part of my assets
You want to make an account with an alias?
I have applied for provisional attachment. Things are progressing one step at a time
You just need to wait for money to fall into your lap
If he asks to put the house up for sale, don't agree to it
Hello Mother.
Time? I only have lunch time?
Then, would you like to eat together?
You too should drink.
Yes.
If Hae Yoon's dad was alive, you could have been having drinks with him.
I am both Hae Yoon's mother and father, I am playing two roles.
For now, don't think of me as her mother, but think of me as her father.
Let's talk as man-to-man.
About the house?
Yes?
Do you look down on my our Hae Yoon?
Oh, no mother, that's not how it is. We will only live in the studio temporarily.
What studio?
It seems you didn't know, but the contract on the apartment is not done yet
so we will live in the studio.
Seriously!
She doesn't tell me these things and takes your side
Don't your parents only have you.
They should help others after they help their own family members.
Since you have a job, you must know. Imagine how long you will have to save up on your salary in order to buy a house
you make even less than Hyeyoon
Do you know it's easy to ask one's parents for money?
This is a good opportunity.
Officially ask your parents to help your marriage. This is the perfect opportunity.
They have an apartment in Gangnam, tell them to give that to you.
My family has an apartment in Gangnam?
You didn't know?
I did not know.
But how did you know?
Ahjumma, another bottle of Sujo here please.
You don't know what do make for a wedding list so I made one for you.
Yes.
- It was hard making that list.
Thank you, Mother.
And don't think about marriage expenses.
Why?
You are going to live in a studio anyway.
All the furniture is built-in in the studio, so you can just go and live there.
Then you will have more strength to prepare for the marriage.
Thank you.
Your family lives in difficult circumstances, so of course I need to give you what I can.
Yes.
Would you like to eat before you go?
Ok then let's eat together then. I should tell Jung Hoon to come early.
Why did you get up?
I should help.
You don't have to do that yet, go wait in Jung Hoon's room.
I'll let you know when it's ready.
I thought you would be bored by yourself, would you like to take a look at this together?
You are working alone for your online shopping, it won't be easy.
Where is there is easy work? People think who shops online.
But look at things now, many people shop online.
Jung Hoon.
Is hyung not here?
- He's probably in the kitchen.
Sunbae, this is my friend Ha Jung Hoon.
Jung Hoon, this is Jung San Jin.
Hello.
- Hello.
Have a seat.
On a first meeting this is the appropriate greeting.
-A company that makes toys?
-Yes, and you're a lawyer.
What is your specialty?
-Anything that makes money.
How do you know this Sunbae? I've met all the people you're close with.
I haven't met up with him in a long while. We used to be in the same club.
Then he should also know Hae Yoon.
You know Hae Yoon?
- Yes.
That girl has grown, back in the day...
- Oppa!
Jung Hoon and Hae Yoon are going to get married.
Ah, congradulations.
Yes.
I get it.
- Why?
Hyung isn't here and Hae Yoon is at my house, so I should get back.
Stay and talk.
Is he mad at me?
He was already feeling bad when he came, don't concern yourself.
Tell me to what extent investors ought to rely on equity for me to defend my managerial rights.
You already know that with your salaries you can not buy a house.
Hae Yoon's salary is more than yours.
How cute, he was kind of chubby.
Do you know how difficult his birth was?
He was 3.5 kilos when he was born and his face was very ugly.
I was very hurt when my older sister told me he was ugly.
Children's looks change a lot. Since when did he become so handsome?
My Jung Woo is very handsome, isn't he?
-Yes.
You came.
Yes
Hye Yoon came over right after finishing work. I should tell the Ahjumma that she can leave now.
Come down, we should eat.
Ok.
Why did you just come?
You knew I was here all alone and yet you still came late.
I was upset after seeing your mother so I stopped by Ki Joong's place.
Where you as upset as me? Do you know what I received today?
-A wedding list.
-Do you know what I received? Sh*t.
I don't know what my mom said to you, but isn't that too much?
I found out for the first time that you make more money than I do.
Why didn't you tell me?
You asked me about my salary.
Did you not tell me because you worried that I would get hurt?
Come eat.
-We will continue this later.
You think that scared me?
What are you two doing?
She's pretty.
It's nice that we are all gathered like this.
I think you are getting prettier.
- Thank you father.
You should lose some weight while you prepare to marry.
I was very slender back then too and was often complimented on my beauty.
She doesn't just lose weight. In the evening she's been exercising,
To get rid of the fat on her arms.
It's good to exercise. But she doesn't look like she has a lot of fat.
Did you see the way these kids were staring at each other?
Did they?
Yes dad, I think she did.
That's not right.
Why are you laughing? Is it funny?
It's just that now it seems like Hye Yoon has really become part of our family.
Since she's comfortable around us she can fully express her feelings in front of us now.
Are you uncomfortable?
-No
So mean.
Do you knowJun Sang Jin?
Why are you asking?
I saw him earlier with Dong Bi at Ki Joong's restaurant.
He said he knows you.
I know him, then what?
I'm just asking.
But why would you suddenly ask that? Out of the blue?
Did that guy like you?
Of course, who wouldn't like me?
I was very popular too.
Of course. You're the son next door who is nice to everyone.
I said brought up something unnecessary. Let's not get upset over something useless.
Finish saying what you were about to earlier.
Let's declare a truce today. Let's end it here, I think my brain is ready to burst.
Fine. Let's not get too emotional, but talk about it once we have thought it own on our own.
Okay. Be careful on your way home.
-Aren't you going to drive me home?
-I'll grab you a taxi. It'll be safer.
Okay. I won't call you out on being pity for not driving me home.
Didn't you drive her home?
She left in a taxi.
Good. You need to go to work tomorrow and if you go all the way to Kangbuk you'll come home late.
Mom. Do we own an apartment in Gangnam?
Did I tell you about that?
-So it's true.
-Who told you about that?
-No one.
-What do you mean no one? Someone must have told you.
We bought it as a retirement fund.
Even though we live here, when we go to Seoul it can be convenient too.
I see. A home?
Yes, a home.
Rather than live in a studio for the first few months, how about just moving directly into the apartment?
So this is why you guys were fighting.
-What do you mean?
-You were fighting earlier.
Hye Yoon was unsatisfied with your living conditions so that's why she was like that towards you.
What's wrong with her?
Thinking about her previous conditions, I even told her that there is no need to think about marriage expenses. Why is she so greedy? When she has nothing to contribute.
-She has the guts of a beggar.
-What wrong with you, Mom?
Without listening to people, you're blaming it all on Hye Yoon.
Then what can I do? You are not even interested in how much money or land we own,
But have you suddenly become ambitious?
I met my mother-in-law earlier.
So what did she say? That we should give up a house?
Was she also the one who mentioned that we have a place in Gangnam?
Please, Mom, just hear me out instead of getting all excited and blaming it all on Hye Yoon.
Go on then.
Mother-in-law raised her child in a difficult situation, all alone.
So in order to ensure that he daughter doesn't suffer, she wants us to buy a house.
Living in a studio with a monthly deposit, how is that suffering?
I didn't have a house so I moved around all the time. Suffering for 10 and 20 years.
I know, and I'm thankful.
I was raised by nice parents who helped me grow, so I never had to worry about those kinds of things.
Mother-in-law is someone who prioritises her family.
She asked if you and Dad don't have any affection for me.
What?
She is not the kind of person do charity.
And if it's for her child then she's ready to take from others.
She's not like you.
Fine. I'll think about it.
You really chose a good person to marry.
I heard you want to marry my sister in law.
You two are the most important things in married life,
but so are the families.
Mrs. Jung is a very unusual person.
What are you doing?
Don`t you see? I´m sleeping in seperate rooms.
Turn off the light on the way out.
Do whatever you want. I don't know what you're thinking.
But it won't go your way.
Damn. It`s not working.
I see how much she is getting stressed by looking at her clean room.
Getting married isn't easy.
It's just the beginning.
When you get married, there is so much to do.
Just think that you're practicing for that.
Where's the nail clipper?
Here it is.
What is this?
(Application for loan)
What are you doing with that?
Is that what you meant by saying you're going to do it by yourself?
You must be out of your mind!
Don't bother. I'm going to pay with my salary.
I can't just let you do it. You're my daughter.
You will know after you have a kid.
What did you tell Jung Hoon?
I told you to stay out of this.
I told you you're only making things worse.
You make money by teaching kids even if you get swollen tonsils.
And even if your back hurts and have to get acupuncture.
Are you saying you're going to suffer for another three years?
I can't let you do that.
Why did you get a loan?
Then what should I do? Mrs. Hae told me to do good wedding gifts.
Are you going to do it?
Can you afford it?
You said you're only going to do nice comforts or whatever.
How am I suppose to discuss stuff like that with you?
So what does she want you to do?
I don't know! I have no idea!
Then don't do this marriage.
You shouldn't do it.
I'll go talk to her tomorrow.
End this.
If I have to, I should be the one who ends this.
I'm doing it because I know you can't.
I knew it when Jung Hoon broke up with you because of his mother.
-He's like an child.
- You're an embarrassment.
You're an embarrassment. I don't want others to know that you're my mom.
I wished you weren't my mom several times.
Why can't she be elegant?
Why doesn't she care what others think of her?
You're proud for yourself because you don't care what other people think.
You're just antisocial!
You're so crazy about a man that you don't even respect your mom.
You think you can me not end it by saying this?
I'm scared.
There's nothing to be scared of.
You don't know because it didn't happen to you.
I can sleep only if I change the password and check if it's lock several times.
It won't happen if you don't mess up with her.
I can't do this. Let's break up.
I don't cling on to someone that leaves me.
Can you still give me this studio?
I will make it under your name.
I hate this studio.
Sell it and give it to me.
You do it. I'm busy.
-Hello?
-This is real estate.
We can't sell your studio.
-You know Jung Hae Jin, right?
- Yes, I do.
Yes, I understand.
I will check it now.
Creditor: Jung Hae Jin.
Ah, this woman.
-Are you really going to be like this?
-What is this about?
A property division claim? Who decided that?
So far we've followed your wishes. You should look forward to see what happens from now.
You're the one who should look forward to see what happens from now on. You know me. I never step down from a fight.
Of course I know. I've stayed by your side for 7 years.
That's why I hurried to secure the savings. You didn't know, right?
You're flustered because you didn't know, right? From now on we'll often run into these situations.
-Don't you dare move an inch and stay right there!
-If I want to go somewhere I'll go, anytime, anywhere!
Stop right there!
A property division claim, Jung Hae Jin?
If we're going to divorce then let's do it! It's money that I earned, what did you do? Are you going to seize my property?
I already told you. That I have the right to at least receive that much. The lawyer told me that was within my rights.
Lawyer? He scammed you.
To get himself a nice fee from you. No matter if you win or lose, he makes money!
You're scared. Worried the property might be taken from you. That's why you ran over here.
Why are you getting lawyers involved?
There is such a thing as an agreement. This is a situation in which an agreement is sufficient!
I wanted to just get an agreement too, but what did you do?
You didn't even try to tell me or split it evenly.
Let's talk from now.
I'll listen to what you want.
I don't think that a property division is an unreasonable demand.
There has been fluctuations in the property prices, and there's no cash flow!
You've removed it.
Not considering the Namyangju hospital site, 5 studios, and the Busan condo, I'll share those half-half.
I'll have custody.
You're still young. Meet a new partner and live with him.
I'll never yield the custody to you. And right now I have no thought about meeting a new man.
Acting as if we were not splitting up, you were moving quietly.
Where did you hide the cash assets?
Did you hand it to that b*tch?
Hold yourself together!
What are you looking at?
I'm right! You sold the studio, to give it to her.
You don't have a problem giving her money, but on me the money is wasted?
While living together you've used an abundance of money.
I've done more for you than your parents!
What kind of agreement can we possibly come to like this?
Okay, let's take this to court. Let's see who wins and who kneels!
Where are you going?
Do I have to be happy that you're suddenly so interested in what I'm doing?
The lawyer is here, right?
He isn't here right now.
I talked with him over the phone and he said that he was here.
He had a prior engagement so he went out of office. You can talk with me.
I've worked here for a long time, so I'm better than most lawyers.
-What kind of tea would you like?
-No need.
My husband found out. About seizing the property. What should I do?
He found out about the seizure, but what measures need to be taken? He can't prevent the seizure on his side anyways.
We should just prepare for court on our side.
Excuse me.
Don't worry too much. Just go home and rest.
We'll take care of business.
How can I not worry? This is the first time something like this has happened to me. And my husband is no push-over.
Then what should we do?
At the very least we should get in contact with the lawyer.
I'm telling you that I'm as good as a lawyer. You just need to talk with me.
How many client do you think we have? How can the lawyer take care of them all?
When the ordination was due you said that you would take care of it, and not to worry, but...
You've never had an office job, right?
Because you've always stayed at home, you don't realize what real life is like.
Doing this much, means doing a lot.
Yes, Aunt?
Can you come over today?
I need to go to visit the elders, but I can't go because of Unnie.
Why?
She won't eat. Is it normal for her not to eat?
I came out during my lunch hour, but she has been like that the entire time.
I fetched som porridge for her, but she hasn't even touched it.
I'm embarrassed because of you! How can you be this embarrassing?
Nevermind. This isn't the time for me to be like this.
Nothing will be resolved if I stay like this.
Things are already like this, I can't become a burden to my kid later on.
I should get something to eat.
No one has ever done anything for me.
As time passes, truth always wins out.
Unnie, you're finally eating!
-Fetch yourself a bowl.
-Of course we should eat!
Unnie, things aren't like they used to be. This doesn't pass easily.
Everything poured out. It feels refreshing now.
In your life, you've done well in marriage.
And the best you've done, is to not have children.
-What about Mom?
-Tae Won?
He has english lessons today so I sent him off.
-Why are you here?
-I heard that you weren't feeling well.
Doing something useless.
Your face looks pale. Let's at least go to the hospital and get some vitamins for you.
There's no use in that.
A garlic drink is good for you. It will get rid of the fatigue.
That's what women with lots of time say when they're ill. I have to open the store.
Take the day off. I'll buy you something nice to eat so let's go out.
Do you also find your mother embarrassing?
It isn't like you to say something like that.
How is your husband?
So-so.
Hearing your talk, there isn't much to do anyways. Latch onto this opportunity and live like that.
Mom. How much do you predict there is to do at the in-law's house?
If it's tolerable, just listen. If it's good, it's good.
Jung Hoon has had everything handed to him on a silver platter. What kind of qualifications does he have? He only has a talen for being patronizing.
If they get married then Hye Yoon has to work all her life to make a living. Why is his parents making demands?
They should be satisfied with the fact that the two of them are getting married.
There's nothing as good as having had everything handed on a silver platter by one's parents.
It wasn't for you to hear. In all honesty, Hye Yoon and I both live well thanks to you.
Really, Mom. In this world no one is like you, Mom...
Whatever.
Mom.
Are you okay?
Fine. Since his parents are well off and educated, why does it matter who he is seeing?
And even if they divorce, then what's wrong with that? The parents will be ready to back him up.
-Mom.
-But even so...
Everything I had an earned I gave to you.
I sold everything worth anything to pass the money to you.
I raised you like that, so how can I watch you in pain?
Do you know the sorrow that comes with having no home?
Do you know how difficult it is to move, even once? So why should either of you get married to someone who doesn't own a house?
I know, Mom. Calm down.
Is marriage a game for kids? Do it wrong once and your entire life is turned around.
As a mother, how can I just stand by an watch that?
Mom.
Mom, Mom, Mom!
Aunt! Aunt!
Unnie, what's wrong?
We need to take her to the hospital.
Why? Are you very sick?
- No, i'm fine.
- Let me see.
Your body temperature is normal.
I told you that i was fine.
I came because the housekeeper said you wouldn't eat or get out of bed.
I just lost my appetite.
Do not bother about the wedding.
Just leave it to the kids.
I would if I trusted them.
There's not a single thing that i approve of.
- Let's just ask for their understanding.
- Then I'll have to meet them. I don't want to.
Should i meet them?
Should i make porridge? I'm pretty good making them.
There's some food in the refrigerator.
Okay.
I'll meet the reporter and leave immediately.
- Tell him to write a good one.
- Don't worry. He is an old classmate.
Go ahead.
[Mom is sick. Because of you. Come home early.]
What is this? I know mink, but not this.
Just think of it as a better fur than mink.
Fur is fur. Why are they doing things more complicated than they should be?
But details like that are important.
How kind of them to let you know what they want.
Should we buy Mother a mink?
She might even throw all of her fur coats if she have this.
You are too into fur.
Oh, there it is!
If i buy this bag, I'll be in bankruptcy.
Let's go.
Hey. Hae Yoon.
- How do you know her?
- We met before.
Dong Bi you must be friends with Jung Hoon and Yoon Hae too.
That's true. We all know each other.
- Did you buy something?
- Not yet.
You already lost interest?
The bags are tempting, but you lose interest fast.
Then I'll leave.
Dong Bi.
I also think you're ridiculous.
Very good Pizza.
Let's leave that at that. I'll wait for the pictures.
I already said i didn't want to. Doesn't that make you feel bad?
It might make me feel bad, but still i want it.
So if i want it, i get it. Because then, i feel better.
I thought chaebol daughters were just given
what they have. But you are aggresive.
Ordinary people don't understand,
but we do what we have to do to survive.
Sounds good. I'll do it.
- Ah, that crazy girl.
- How can se be so catty?
We are all human. We fight back when we have to.
- Can't turn it down.
- Don't you have a limit?
- I don't even know how it looks like.
- Yeah good luck to you.
This is not time to care about other people.
Now what do i do?
Good for her. She can buy things like that because she's rich.
Wow you sure have changed.
You didn't use to envy things like that.
That's because what is a problem for me isn't a problem for her.
Jung Hoon's mother is nice though.
I think marriage makes people strange.
Why else would she give a list so ridiculous?
Be careful. You're talking about Jung Hoon's mother.
Then don't complain about her to me!
- Didn't you say you had problems with her?
- I admit it. It's true.
_ Who is it?
- My aunt. She fought with my mom.
It's all pointless stuff.
At the end, my aunt always sides with my mother.
I see it's reached your family too. Everyone seems to be fighting.
Now that i think about it, there's
one more fight to look forward to.
This is our new product, isn't it cool?
How is this a new product?
It's upgraded. The body's new.
Dude. If i write an article, i need something to write about.
Next time, bring a product worth reviewing. I'm going.
Take this and give it to the kids.
Tell them to play with it.
You punk. Alright. Stop by some time.
Goodbye.
- Hello?
- Did you meet the reporter?
- Yeah
- Are you still meeting with him?
- It's over.
- We have to finish our conversation.
We should. But not today. I have work to do at home.
My mom is not feeling well.
Are you making excuses because you don't want to talk with me?
You are still upset, right?
Should i show you the text to prove it?
- I'm sorry for getting upset.
- It's fine now.
But still, thank you for coming to see my mother.
No, of course i have to go and see her. The housekeeper is leaving early also.
At times like this, i realize that i chose my woman well.
This is just a teaser. In time I'll show you just how awesome a woman I am.
I think my dad will like it too.
-Let's by bream. I'm good at making steamed bream.
-Okay.
Mom is sick. Come home early.
It's my sister. She says my mother is sick and wants me to come home early.
-Then you have to go.
-She's doing it in vain. I fought with my mom last night.
Is it really okay for you not to go?
Yes. If my mom was a car, she would be a SUV. She's sturdy.
-Has mom has her health checked?
-She probably hasn't.
It's mandatory, why hasn't she had it done?
Since we're here, let's get the check-up too.
There shouldn't be anything wrong, right?
It's scary to see someone who has never before been sick in her life like this.
-Aunt, go on home. I'll stay.
-Don't worry about Tae Won, I'll pick him up on my way back.
-Thank you, Aunt.
-No need to thank me, it's only natural.
Hye Yoon hasn't even called.
-Come on in. We see each often, it's nice.
-Me too.
-Mom, are you sick?
-I'm okay.
You don't have a fever.
It's neurological. After eating and talking with us, she'll be fine.
Mom, Hye Yoon said she would make you dinner.
Mother-in-law, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay. But do you know how to cook?
Yes. I've known how to cook since high school.
Really? Lately I hear that girls don't really know how to cook until after they marry.
Hye Yoon might even be a better cook than you, Mom.
I have high expectations now.
No, you shouldn't, Father-in-law.
-What are you looking for?
-An apron.
-She didn't look very sick.
-You're right.
-My father is a little sensitive to my mother.
-He's going a little overboard.
When I heard that she was sick, I thought that she couldn't even get out of bed.
It's good that she isn't sick. Do you feel wronged because you have to make dinner? Should we just order in?
It's fine. I came here to cook for her, how can we just order in?
But do you really know how to cook?
During the time we've been together, you've never made me anything to eat.
It's tasted good.
No, that's not right.
This isn't just good.
It's excellent!
-Thank you
-Dad, I was really shocked. I feel cheated.
She had never cooked for me before.
Really?
I only wanted to cook for the man I was to marry so I was saving my skill.
Our son is a real winner!
That kind of attitude is good too. I don't like careless kids.
Mother-in-law, you are really clear on what you like and dislike.
Shall I try the soup too?
This tasted good too.
You treat me differently now that I've cooked for you.
Last time you told me to get a taxi, but this time you're driving me home.
You thought that was all? There's more.
What is this place?
It's my family's country house. Let's sleep here tonight.
What about work tomorrow? And school?
It's possible to commute for here. I'll drop you off.
Our parents will understand too. We're about to get married after all.
We're about to get married, but we aren't married yet. Let's just go home.
We came all this way...
Then let's rest a bit before we go.
Don't touch me. I'm ovulating. Are you going to take responsibility?
- It hurts. Don't laugh.
- But it's funny!
Oh hold on. I have a message.
[Strike Out]
Why aren't you answering? If it's the family, I'll talk to them myself.
- Is he an ex?
- I know, right?
Answer it. Why can't you? Is something holding you back?
Why would something hold me back?
Hello?
Hey Hae Yoon. Do you know where I am?
The lawyer's desk.
This is my office. I had a drink with my colleagues.
You should go home if you've had a drink. Why call me?
I saw the man you're going to marry.
What about when you were with me? Did your standards change?
Were you into guys that ordinary?
If you drank, you should go in and sleep.
Oh, you were with him.
This is too much. How can you be so forward in our first meeting?
We're getting married soon!
Why did you hang up? I had more to say.
What is this jerk?
He's not the only one with a woman to marry.
You're not really a couple until you walk down the altar and tie the knot.
Why didn't you tell me you dated him?
It was for a little while, and it didn't mean anything. Do I still have to tell you?
You said you didn't have any relationship with him.
You really want to know? It'll probably bother you.
Was it that deep of a relationship?
- Do you not trust me?
- You're acting suspicious!
You're my first. The first one I slept with.
For my first, so much, I...
You know how much temptation I turned away?
And you think this isn't my first? Why are you bringing this up?
Is it my fault that he called me drunk?
She'll probably think I'm clingy if I freak out over her past.
Asshole!
I was in a good mood, and he ruined it.
- Did you just curse?
- Because I'm upset!
You curse when you're upset.
I can let other things go but not cursing.
Why didn't you say anything when this guy said I looked ordinary?
That upset me more.
But you are ordinary. What's wrong with that?
He didn't mean it in a good way. What did he say before that?
What... he said you had standards before, but now you don't.
He's saying he's disappointed you're marrying me. Doesn't that make you mad?
It doesn't. Everyone has different values. I want someone who's normal.
That's why I chose you.
Standards? Forget it. He can have standards.
Why are you mad? Is something bothering you?
Want to get hit?
I want my man to be confident no matter what.
Don't become so insecure because of something as small as that.
What are you saying? Because he's a lawyer, and I'm just a salaryman, you assume I'm insecure?
I've never valued myself based on what my job is.
I see now you have more in common with your mother than I thought!
If I thought the same thing as my mother, I wouldn't meet you.
I have my standards too.
I don't want a guy that's successful. I want a guy that's going to be by my side.
I thought you were that kind of guy. Are you not?
Don't you remember what your father said? You're the only man who can have me.
I like Hae Yoon the more I see her.
I really do like her. She's good with her hands.
Most girls wouldn't admit they cooked for themselves when they were younger.
But she said it proudly.
- She's pretty.
- She is.
How about we think about setting up a house for the kids?
What about the deposit?
We'll cover the moving expenses and take care of anything else.
Our son is falling under the spell of his woman.
If that's what you think, I'll follow through.
- As expected, you are my soulmate.
- Just a soulmate?
Of course not. Let's take a shower.
Hey how can you just get off?
Take care of this.
I went to go buy the bag your mother wanted and gave up.
How can she carry around a car's worth on her arm?
It's a different culture.
I thought you said you'd do anything for me.
Fine, I'll take care of it.
- Don't say I made you do it.
- Fine. I'm not stupid.
I'll forgive you.
That's not enough.
I'll give that to you when you earn it.
Fox. Fox. She's a wily fox.
Sis. No one's home.
I'm at the hospital.
Why are you there?
- Did you get my text or not?
- I did.
But you just ignored it? And ignored Aunt's phone call too. What were you doing?
I went to Jung Hoon's house. I didn't know Mom was very sick.
I even sent you text message about it. How couldn't you know?
And if you don't know, then just ask.
I'll go there now.
There's no need. She's getting discharged.
Excuse me!
I'll do it. Making efforts all day long.
Efforts? You heard the doctor, right?
You've overworked yourself all this time and your body needs to rest.
So just rest. Do you want to go to the spa with me?
I hate it when it's too hot and tiresome.
Tiresome? It's just going somewhere to relax.
I'll go on my own, so you just go home.
I'm going to sleep with you tonight.
-What about your husbands?
-Even without me he'll be fine.
Don't act as if you know me, and just go to your car.
I told you to go to your car, what are you doing?
Okay.
Oppa, are we playing detective right now?
-It's possible that my wife is having us followed.
-Wow, so does that mean that we can't meet?
Are you asking if we are breaking up?
That was before I found out that you are divorcing your wife.
-Come to the studio.
-Not the studio.
Let's go somewhere else. The hotel we went to before.
Watch out that you're not being tailed.
Okay.
You jerk, get out!
I know that I bumped into you but...
How much is she paying you?
-What are you talking about?
-I've caught you.
Come out!
Where's the camera? Where is it?
Someone report this! Someone call the police! Report this!
Where is the camera?
Do you think it's okay for a community leader to act like this?
I'm sorry.
He stopped his car on purpose too.
I'm sorry. Come out to my hospital, I'll treat you.
I'll take care of my own car, and I'll pay for your repairs.
Just do like that.
Do you handle aesthetics too? My skin isn't too good because of pimples.
We don't have that. But instead I'll get your laser treatment.
That isn't something that can be handled with a massage.
I think there was a misunderstanding. I'll settle.
Just do that.
In that case...
Are you a kid? Coming out from the police station at your age.
-Wear your helmet.
-I don't want to wear it.
-What if we get caught?
-I've already gotten caught. Do you think it's scary to get caught a second time?
After switching over once, you just leave like that.
Since I switched over once, I know the value of the things I protected this far.
Let's go!
Hold on!
He really doesn't listen.
Where did you go? I asked you to stay home
ER
why?
I told you we are coming
I was trying to lighten my guilt by running around
No matter how cold-hearted you try to pretend, you are soft at heart in the end.
Why do you throw a temper when you're soft-hearted like that?
Is mom okay?
It's because of her personality
She's not the type to bend but break
I wore your PJs
go ahead
I am gonna sleep with mom in her room, do you want to join?
Are you okay?
Of course I am ok
I am sorry
No need. You're just saying it
I reflected a lot.
Then cancel your loan.
You can't?
If you get married and have a baby right away, you have to take care of the baby and take a leave from work.
When you can go to school again, you have to take care of the child.
Living like that you can't gather any money.
I said this to Jung Hoon too. Receive a share from his parents and start well off.
Mom, you're back to yourself.
Is it true that you were sick?
Think carefully about this.
I've lived through it so I know. What you see, that's all you have.
House, Face and clothes. You can't play games with these.
Unnie, Mom is at it again.
Mom, just stop it today.
Cancel your loan.
-You took out a loan?
-She took out three thousand!
That's why I'm angry.
You should have told me. I told you that I would help.
Don't you do anything either! I won't stand for it!
Get out, both of you! I'm going to sleep!
We were going to sleep here tonight.
Why would we sleep together in a cramped place like this?
I can't sleep with her!
Unnie. Two daughters laying down next to their mother,
If you wanted a beautiful picture like that, then isn't this good enough?
To snore like that isn't good. They say that sleep apnea means that the heart is at unrest.
When menopause hits, the female hormons increase.
Then I'll soon be like that too.
Annie you still have far to go. How can a woman of 30 get menopause?
I've unknowingly aged.
Doesn't your husband hold you often enough?
That's not something a virgin should say.
Unnie, I'm only a virgin according to the law.
You know about that night.
So that's what it was? Our Hye Yoon is now grown up to the point of having these kinds of conversations.
I'm going to sleep.
To buy all of this, we'll need at least 100 million won.
After saying we wouldn't do it, we'll end up like beggars.
This isn't possible with our abilities.
Maybe there's a way to compromise.
Engagement party invitation.
I came out early to give it to you.
It's already ready. It's pretty!
-Are you even having an engagement party?
-Her family wanted it.
Since they didn't have a wedding themselves, it seems like they want us to have it all.
Hyung!
He brought over an invitation to the engagement party.
Good. I wanted to see you.
Just one cup of tea.
I had a favor to ask so I followed you out. Gather some money for me.
How much?
-100 million won.
-What are you going to spend it on?
-It's for the marriage preparations.
-What is there for you to prepare? Isn't Aunt doing it for you?
It's not because of Mom, it's because of Hye Yoon.
Since her circumstances are kind of bad.
Listen to what I have to say carefully, and don't get upset.
100 million won is a lot of money.
Even if you put aside your entire salary, it'll take a few years to make that kind of money.
If you aren't going to lend it to me, then don't. Your excuse is too long.
That's right. I won't lend it to you.
It's not because the money would be wasted, but because there's another reason for you.
It hasn't even been 100 years since marriage for love has been implemented.
Studies say that the maximum amount of time for any one love to last is around 3 years.
Hyung, I still believe that there is such a thing as eternal love.
The results of a study like that also changes depending on who did it and on what premise.
I'm saying this because I care about you.
The moment you decide to marry her you're lowering yourself to a different class the then one you belong in.
You think this will be the last time you ask for money?
You and I truly do think differently. It's not a question of who is right or wrong,
but it doesn't make me feel good.
Are you angry?
If it's for Hye Yoon, then I can take all the beating in the world.
I'm thinking that she was right after all.
I'm off.
International phone call
Hello?
What are you doing?
Why did you take so long to answer the phone? Are you already asleep?
Why are you calling me instead of sleeping?
Don't worry, I was about to go to bed.
Why would I worry about you?
When I was 7, it felt like Hell to walk up that mountain, right?
Why are you suddenly mentioning that?
Is it because of your father?
Then go ahead, it doesn't scare me at all.
Must be nice not to be scared of your father.
But, how can refer to Dad as my father?
I don't have a Dad. Did you forget that I got kicked out?
Kicked out? Who left the house first?
What's the use in talking about the past?
Are you drinking?
I'm drinking.
Crazy bastard. Doing well...
Spending money, spending money. Why did he send you to America?
Talk to Dad about that.
Whatever. Am I your messenger?
If you're 22, then talk to him yourself.
Such a complicated life...
Lawyer Kim? Yes?
Is it too late now?
Is everything ready?
You definitely have to take action!
Saury Kimchi stew! It's been a long time since we had this.
There wasn't much to eat in the refrigerator so I went to the supermarket to buy this.
Even though three women live here, the refrigerator is really empty.
It's because she's taking everything out.
Unnie, that isn't true!
-Are you dating someone
-No way...
It isn't Min Ho Ahjussi, right?
Aunt and Min Ho Ahjussi? No way! That Ahjussi doesn't look at women older than 30.
I wouldn't like him either.
Don't even mention him. It makes me lose my appetite.
I'm saying this just in case, but you can't date that Ahjussi.
I'm close to Tae Won's father so I know. He doesn't have a shred of responsibility.
Why do you think he got divorced twice? Let's say the first time was a mistake.
But a second time? That means there's something wrong with him.
The competent once can get divorced twice or three times.
-It looks like he has a lot of money.
-Mom!
Look at the Hollywood stars. They had money and pretty faces, so they get divorced several times.
You have to be competitive to divorce like that.
The worst are those who refuse to divorce and refuse to spend any money.
Our Mom certainly follows the trends.
Since your Mom has daughters like you, if you look at her lifestyle, she certainly is a feminist.
Mom. Mother-in-law said that we don't have to worry about marriage expenses.
I sure am grateful.
Then does it make sense for you to enter that kind of household and have to uphold the marriage expenses too?
I made a mistake. I thought you were in a good mood.
It seems like you misunderstood something. Just because we're having a meal together doesn't mean that I forgive you.
Unnie!
I'm getting more vexed the more I think about it.
I raised my kids to the point of ruining my body, and then you tell me that I embarrass you.
Yes, Jung Hoon's mother?
Hello? Is this a good time?
Yes, it's a good time.
And anyways, I wanted to meet with you.
I also called because I wanted to meet with you.
When would be a good time?
Yes.
Yes, okay.
Jung Hoon's mother? We're in-laws, why does she refer to me as Jung Hoon's mother?
That means that you're uncomfortable, right, Hye Yoon's mother?
I came to talk to you about the issue of our kid's housing.
It seems like you're beating around the bush.
What do you mean?
Maybe it's because I haven't had much, but I would give everything I have to my children.
Sure I can momentarily be thankful to the people who give to charity. But in the end, when my body hurt and I'm in pain, then it's only right to lean on your children.
Charity is not only something you do to make others happy, but also for your own happiness.
Of course it's natural to also ensure our children's properties.
But for them to start paying monthly rent is a little... It's not like you don't own a house. And isn't it true that you also have a spare house?
What's this, now?
Rich people usually own more houses.
What does she know to talk like that?
Just by looking at your outfit, your skin, and your jewelry, there is no mistake that you are the wife of a tycoon.
If you spend this much on your looks, then isn't is obvious?
I don't know if it's a compliment or criticism.
Even if she sold her wardrobe, I bet it could buy a house.
It's a compliment of course, how could I criticize you, Jung Hoon's mother?
You've called me Jung Hoon's mother since you called, Hye Yoon's mother!
Since you refer to me like that, it reminds me of when the kids went to school and I used to meet up with the other mothers.
Yes I feel the same. It has been a long time since I meet up with the children's friend's parents.
And to be able to speak honestly.
When did she not speak honestly?
Of course it's nice.
It's true that we do not only own one house.
I discussed it with my husband, and we already decided to not have the kids pay monthly rent to begin with. And we decided to end the contract with our current tenant.
Oh, is that right?
The last time I meet Hye Yoon, I told her not to worry about the marriage expenses, but since the situation is different now, it seems only right for you to handle the marriage expenses.
Instead of Gangbuk, don't you have an apartment or something in Gangnam?
An apartment in Gangnam?
Do you have an apartment in Gangnam?
Yes we do. How did you know that?
Did you do a background check on us?
A background check?
Did you come to our house?
-Kang Hye Jin?
-Yes
Can I see some ID? And please sign here.
Here it is.
Where did it come from?
-The courthouse.
-What is it, Mom?
I don't know.
Divorce lawsuit papers.